Power corrupts.
Code 8 Part II is a science fiction, action, crime film directed by Jeff Chan.
In a world where superpowered people are heavily policed by robots, an ex-con teams
up with a drug lord he despises to protect a teen from a corrupt cop.
Connor, played by Robbie Amell.
Garrett, played by Stephen Amell.
Sergeant 'King' Kingston, played by Alex Mallari Jr..
Pavani, played by Sirena Gulamgaus.
Detective Davis, played by Aaron Abrams.
Officer Cirelli, played by Moe Jeudy-Lamour.
Code 8: Part II is a 2024 Canadian superhero science fiction action film directed by Jeff Chan,
who co-wrote the screenplay with Chris Paré, Sherren Lee and Jesse LaVercombe.
It is a sequel to the 2019 film Code 8.
Robbie Amell and Stephen Amell reprise their roles from the original film as Connor Reed and Garrett Kelton, respectively; Sirena Gulamgaus, Altair Vincent,
Alex Mallari Jr., Moe Jeudy-Lamour, Aaron Abrams, and Jean Yoon also star, with Abrams and Mallari reprising their roles from the original film.
Code 8: Part II was released on Netflix on February 28, 2024.
The tone is thought_provoking.